// Creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "The following are common characteristics of flash fiction EXCEPT ______.",
    answer: "b. in panel images",
    options: [
      "a. brief",
      "b. in panel images",
      "c. has complete plot",
      "d. presents twists in the ending"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "“The Barn Owl’s Wondrous Capers” by Sarnath Banerjee is a/an ______.",
    answer: "b. flash fiction",
    options: [
      "a. epic",
      "b. flash fiction",
      "c. melodrama",
      "d. graphic novel"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Flash fiction is also known as______.",
    answer: "a. Nanotales",
    options: [
      "a. Nanotales",
      "b. short story",
      "c. graphic fiction",
      "d. macro stories"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which flash fiction story tells how anyone can buy a perfect clone Taylor Swift at his doorstep?",
    answer: "c. “Clone of Taylor Swift”",
    options: [
      "a. “Taylor Swift”",
      "b. “Unnecessary Things”",
      "c. “Clone of Taylor Swift”",
      "d. “Angels and Blueberries”"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which is a feature of a graphic novel?",
    answer: "d. It encourages interactivity in the minds of the reader as he fills in the blank between pages.",
    options: [
      "a. A Graphic novel is in condensed form.",
      "b. It presents micro-stories in each sub-plot.",
      "c. The main character victoriously attained his purpose in the story.",
      "d. It encourages interactivity in the minds of the reader as he fills in the blank between pages."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "“In the Shadow of No Towers: 9/11” by Art Spiegelman is a/an ______.",
    answer: "c. graphic novel",
    options: [
      "a. epic",
      "b. flash fiction",
      "c. graphic novel",
      "d. tragic drama"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "It is imaginative literature ranges from a word to a thousand.",
    answer: "c. flash fiction",
    options: [
      "a. Tales",
      "b. short story",
      "c. flash fiction",
      "d. graphic fiction"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "A flash fiction presents a surprising ending which means that ______.",
    answer: "d. the story ends with a twist.",
    options: [
      "a. it ends happily.",
      "b. it ends tragically.",
      "c. it has a loose ending.",
      "d. the story ends with a twist."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "It refers to comic narratives in which pictures are arranged in sequence in image panels.",
    answer: "d. graphic fiction",
    options: [
      "a. comic story",
      "b. storyboard",
      "c. flash fiction",
      "d. graphic fiction"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which is not TRUE about graphic novel?",
    answer: "c. Graphics novel presents fewest words as possible.",
    options: [
      "a. It combines letters and words.",
      "b. Image panels are very colorful.",
      "c. Graphics novel presents fewest words as possible.",
      "d. Illustrations allow the readers to imagine and experience the characters and events in the story."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "Dialogues in graphic fiction are written in ______.",
    answer: "c. speech bubbles",
    options: [
      "a. text boxes",
      "b. image panels",
      "c. speech bubbles",
      "d. beside illustrations"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "“Louis Riel” of Chester Brown centers on a fictionalized violent rebellion in the 19th century is an example of the literary genre.",
    answer: "a. Graphic novel",
    options: [
      "a. Graphic novel",
      "b. Text-talk novel",
      "c. Melodramatic play",
      "d. Flash fictional story"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "This story narrates the traumatic experiences of Americans during the 9/11 terrorists attack in New York.",
    answer: "d. “In the Shadow of No Towers: 9/11”",
    options: [
      "a. “Louis Riel”",
      "b. “Unnecessary Things”",
      "c. “The Barn Owl’s Wondrous Capers”",
      "d. “In the Shadow of No Towers: 9/11”"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "Graphic fiction is also known as ______.",
    answer: "c. graphic fiction",
    options: [
      "a. digi-fiction",
      "b. flash fiction",
      "c. graphic fiction",
      "d. doodle fiction"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "Which does NOT belong to the group?",
    answer: "c. Text-talk novel",
    options: [
      "a. Tragedy",
      "b. Flash fiction",
      "c. Text-talk novel",
      "d. Graphic fiction"
    ]
  },
];
